{
    "subject": "resource/Reshmi_Ghosh",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Ghosh, Reshmi",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Reshmi Ghosh is Ghosh, Reshmi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9817116260528564,
            "question": "What is the full name of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9226486682891846,
            "question": "What is Reshmi Ghosh's last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8997576832771301,
            "question": "Does Reshmi Ghosh have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889927864074707,
            "question": "Is Reshmi Ghosh a male or female name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8649597764015198,
            "question": "How many parts make up Reshmi Ghosh's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8171071410179138,
            "question": "What is the order of Reshmi Ghosh's first and last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076570630073547,
            "question": "What does the name 'Reshmi' mean?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522432208061218,
            "question": "Is 'Ghosh' a common last name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6844897866249084,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Reshmi Ghosh, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06944583356380463,
            "question": "Can you think of someone else with the same first name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Reshmi Ghosh is Ghosh, Reshmi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8713_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to introduce Reshmi Ghosh, what would you say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8713_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Ghosh' a common last name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8713_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the name 'Reshmi' mean?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8713_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8713_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text snippets do not state the full name of Reshmi Ghosh as \"Ghosh, Reshmi\". \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about the full name of Reshmi Ghosh being \"Ghosh, Reshmi.\" They mainly discuss her acting career and some biographical details but do not provide a full name in that format."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests Reshmi Ghosh's full name includes her surname. Only her first name is mentioned repeatedly, and there is no mention of her surname.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context consistently lists \"Reshmi Ghosh\" as her full name.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of her full name being Ghosh, Reshmi in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context uses \"Reshmi Ghosh\" as the name without any initial or middle names, suggesting it is a full name. Additionally, there is no information supporting that her full name is just \"Ghosh, Reshmi.\"",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}